Toni Morrison Papers, 1917-2015: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1917-2015; 66 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Novels, 1917-2015; 1970-2015; 66 boxes
    - Love, 1999 January 28-2003; 7 boxes
      - Chapter 5: Lover, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - "She never took her eyes off the trays...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
          Pages 7-19.
        - "Sandler admitted he could have imagined the look...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 6: Husband, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Chapter 7, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 6: Husband, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 July 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 July 8; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - "no one to stop him...", circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
          Pages 12-15.
        - Chapter 6: Husband, 2002 July 8; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 November 13; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - "Correctional girls knew better...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - "Correctional girls knew better...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - L4, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - L4, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, June 3 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, 2002 June 3; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, 2002 September 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L, 2002 September 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, 2002 November 13; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - L4, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - "dollar bill, May said...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
          Pages 6-10.
        - "You are always thinking about death...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - "dress and started in.", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
          Pages 4, 6, 10.
        - "You are always thinking about death...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 7: Guardian, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Chapter 7: Guardian, 2002 August 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 7, 2002 August 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 7: Guardian, 2002 August 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 7, 2002 December 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - "the door and asked her if she could take Romen on as after school help...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
          Pages 5-11.
        - "Uneasy with other men's sexual confidences...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
          Pages 6-18.
        - "I don't know what to say to the boy...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - "me. You'd have taken care of me.", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
          Pages 20-21.
        - "I don't know what to say to the boy...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 8: Father, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Chapter 8: Father, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 13; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 13; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 26; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8: Father, 2002 September 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8: Father, 2002 November 11; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 November 11; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - "The hiking boots...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - End of Chapter 8, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - "anticipation, she felt kind, generous...", circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
          Page 20.
        - "The hiking boots...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - "The hiking boots...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - "The hiking boots...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 9: Phantom, 2001 July 15; 1 folder
        - Chapter 12 (Material for final chapter), undated; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - SW Chapter 10, 2001 July 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "[They begin to talk]", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
          Pages 3-15.
        - Chapter 10 (Material for), circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 10: Phantom, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 9: Phantom, June 6 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "Am I?", circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
          Page 17.
        - Chapter 9, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - 9, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "Heed can't look...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "Heed can't look...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "Heed can't look...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - "Junior, huddled over her knees...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
          Pages 309-310.
        - "Junior, huddled over her knees...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - L5, 2002 June 27-September 26; 2 folders
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
          Page 3.
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - "Sometimes children fall in love...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - "Sometimes children fall in love...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L5, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L, 2002 June 27; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - L5, 2002 September 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - "I see you...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - "for a glimpse of blood...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
          Pages 3-6.
        - "I see you...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - "I see you...", circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Love Drafts, 2002 June-2003 January 29; 2 boxes
        - Love Draft, as L, 2002 June-September; Printout. 1 item (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Love Draft, as L, 2002 October 1; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
        - Love Draft, as L, 2003 January 29; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
          Pages 1-317. With Robert Gottlieb's annotations.
        - Love Draft, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
          Pages 1-317.
        - Love Miscellaneous Corrected Pages, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Love Draft, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
          Pages 1-319.
        - Love Draft, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 45, Folder 4-5)
        - Love Draft, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
      - Love Rough Page Proofs, 2003 April 29; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 1)
        Pages a-b, i-iv, 1-218; with 5 notepad pages of corrections.
      - Love Rough Page Proofs Author's Set, 2003 April 23; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 2)
        Pages a-b, i-iv, 1-218. With letters from Diana Terjerina at Knopf, dated November 3, 2003 and December 8, 2004.
      - Love Revised Page Proofs #1, 2003 June 24; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
      - Essence Excerpt, 2003 July 18; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
        With correspondence between Toni Morrison, Tracy Allen at Essence, and Liz Farrell at ICM.
      - Love Third Pass Pages, 2003 August 20; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
        With letter from Margaux Wexberg at Knopf, dated August 20, 2003.
      - Love Revised Page Proofs #2 Master Set, 2003 August 22; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 7)
        Pages [1]-[202].
      - Love Advance Copy, 2003; 1 item (Box 47, Folder 1)
        Pages [1]-[202]. PR blurb edited by Toni Morrison.
      - Love Design/Production, 2003; 2 folders (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - A Mercy, 2004-2009; 9 boxes
      Early outlines and drafts include material relating to Home and God Help the Child.
      - A Mercy Research Material, circa 2004-2008; 2 boxes
        - Research Material, circa 2004-2008; 6 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-6)
        - Research Material, circa 2004-2008; 5 folders (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
      - Notes for Proposal, circa 2006-2008; Notepad pages. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Outlines and Notes, circa 2006-2008; Printout and handwritten notes. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Chronology/Outline: Mercy 3/Florens, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - "He moved carefully through the water...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - "Now in an abyss...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - "The man moved carefully...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - "To purposefully throw oneself...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - "Trust me.", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - "...leather.", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - "Lila", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - "Don't be afraid...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - "I stop by a rock...", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - "Dear S.", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - "inserts Rebekka", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - "Add:", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - "1. Florens 1st per.", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - "Examining her body", circa 2006-2008; Notepad. 1 item (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Mercy One, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Mercy Two, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Mercy Three, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Manuscripts [Early Drafts], 2006; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, 2006; 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Florens story, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
          Toni Morrison has required the Library to make surrogate copies of all of her manuscripts (including typescripts and proofs) and diaries (appointment books), including but not restricted to those damaged by fire in 1993. This is for conservation reasons, to prevent damage and deterioration by repeated use. Researchers are required to use digital surrogates in the reading room of the Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.s.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-32.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Florens [Early Drafts], undated; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, circa 2006-2008; 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - A Mercy Draft, June 26 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-38.
        - "Tk 4: Lila...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
          Pages 21-24.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - A Mercy Draft, July 9 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-44.
        - "leaves darkness behind and the dark is me...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
          Pages 41-42.
      - A Mercy Drafts, 2006 December 10-2008; 5 boxes (2 partial)
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Florens", 2006 December 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - A Mercy Draft, 2006 December 13; Printout. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - "before all light is over...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 5)
          Pages 23-26.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-50.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-52.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 8)
          Pages 1-56.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 9)
          Pages 1-60.
        - "Now I am thinking another thing...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 10)
          Pages 7-64.
        - "Seated at last...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 11)
          Pages 20-70.
        - "Jacob Vaark galloped along...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 51, Folder 12)
          Pages 7-75.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-83.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-90.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-91.
        - "Jacob Vaark galloped along...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 4)
          Pages 7-96.
        - "Lila could not bear to enter...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 5)
          Pages 33-63.
        - "She did not mind when they called her Sorrow...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 6)
          Pages 82-104 (pencil 112).
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-115.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 8)
          Pages 1-123.
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Mercy", circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - "Since your leaving with no goodbye...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 1)
          Pages 42-174.
        - "Don't be afraid...", circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - "Don't be afraid...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-40.
        - "How long will it take...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 4)
          Pages 81-119.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-192.
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Mercy", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-197.
        - "Don't be afraid...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - "Don't be afraid...", circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - "Listen to me, she is saying...", circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 9)
          Pages 151-166.
        - "absence was hardly noticed...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 10)
          Pages 183-199.
        - "When he left Mistress' room, Lina followed...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 11)
          Pages 179-199.
        - A Mercy Revised Pages, circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 12)
          Various revised pages.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 13)
          Pages 1-207.
        - "ony. Relying on memory and her own resources...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 14)
          Pages 65-89.
        - "I walk the night through...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 15)
          Pages 214-220.
        - "I dream a dream that dreams back at me...", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 16)
          Pages 192-219.
        - A Mercy Revised Pages, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 53, Folder 17)
          Revised pages, unnumbered.
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Mercy", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
          Pages 1-227.
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Untitled", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
          Pages 1-234.
        - A Mercy Draft, as "Mercy", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
          Pages 1-237.
        - A Mercy Draft, circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected (photocopy). 1 item (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
          Pages 1-241.
        - "Silence. 'You will stay the night?'", circa 2006-2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 54, Folder 9)
          Pages 190-233.
        - "Silence. 'You will stay the night?'", circa 2006-2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - A Mercy Draft, 2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
          Pages 1-241. With Robert Gottlieb's annotations and correspondence from Robert Gottlieb's assistant Sarah Rothbard, dated January 15, 2008.
        - A Mercy Draft, 2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
          Pages 1-241. With Robert Gottlieb's edits transferred in red pencil.
        - A Mercy Revised Pages, circa 2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 55, Folder 5)
          Revised pages.
      - A Mercy Bound Manuscript, 2008; Printout. 1 item (Box 55, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-241. With note from Sarah Rothbard, assistant to Robert Gottlieb, dated February 8, 2008.
      - A Mercy Setting Copy, 2008; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
        Pages b, i-iv, 1-[242].
      - A Mercy Author's Set First Pass Rough Pages, 2008 March 21; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 1)
        Pages b, i-iv,1-172.
      - A Mercy First Pass Page Proofs, 2008 March 21; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 2)
        Pages a-b, i-iv, 1-172. With letter from Sarah Rothbard, assistant to Robert Gottlieb, dated March 27, 2008.
      - A Mercy Author's Set Second Pass Page Proofs, 2008 May 15; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 3)
        Pages a-b, i-iv, 1-170.
      - A Mercy Advance Copy, 2008; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 4)
        Pages 1-167.
      - A Mercy Design/Production, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Home, 1948-2012; 2008-2012; 6 boxes
      Working title Frank Money.
      - Home Research Files, 1948-2011; 2 boxes
        - 1950s, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - The American City H 20, 1948-1951; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Atlanta Tram/Bus, 1977-1981; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Georgia Department of Public Health Report, 1951; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - Georgia H 20, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Georgia Legislature Role in H 20 Supply, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - The Green Book, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - Greyhound Bus Routes: Seattle-Chicago-Atlanta, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - High Cotton, 2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Korea, 1959-2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Life Magazine, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - Military Pay & Benefits, 2003-2010; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous, 1950-2011; portions of 2 boxes
          - Miscellaneous, 1950-2011; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
          - Miscellaneous, 1950-2011; 4 folders (Box 58, Folder 1-4)
        - Miscellaneous Atlanta Constitution, 1952; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - Quilts, 2006; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Rents: Atlanta, 1952 April; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Restaurants of Seattle 1853-1960, 2010; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Sanitary City, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Seattle Central District Housing, 2010; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Southeast Drainage Basins, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - Trains: Chicago-Atlanta, 1952; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - Trains: Portland-Chicago, 1952; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - Wages: Atlanta, 1952 April; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - Weather: Atlanta, 1952 April; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Proposal and Outlines, circa 2008-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - "Cee/rescue", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - "On the bees", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - "p. 25 Decent women delivered babies at home...", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - "Frank's return home", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - "Cee sitting in Ethel's backyard gardens", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - "The eruptions (s. shock incidents)", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - "I can tell now...", circa 2005-2011; Notepad. 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - "Memoire", circa 2005-2011; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Nothings II [Outline and Early Draft], circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Frank Money and Bride [Outline and Early Draft], circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Home Drafts, circa 2005-2011; 3 boxes (1 partial)